Finding aid for Lon G. Nungesser Hope for Humanity Papers, 1970-1989
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- Photo Albums
  - Photo Album Five: The Life and Times of Lonnie Gene Nungesser
    - Flyers distributed before my first signing for Notes... (Volume 5, Page 80-81)
    - A Display case in San Francisco (Volume 5, Page 82)
    - Bill & I before I spoke (Volume 5)
    - The audience gathers before I speak (Volume 5, Page 83)
    - Bill talking with another person from New York (Volume 5)
    - After this appearance a few lingered to chat (Volume 5)
    - Photos of my first autographing session (Volume 5, Page 84)
    - Clipping from the S.F. Chronicle (Volume 5, Page 85)
    - Review of Notes... in The Stanford Daily (Volume 5, Page 86)
    - Interview with me and a Review of Notes... in Au Courant, East Coast distribution (Volume 5, Page 87)
    - Review of Notes... in Stanford Book News (Volume 5, Page 88)
    - Review of Notes... (Volume 5, Page 89)
    - A tanned and toned Lon at his 35th birthday (Volume 5, Page 90)
    - Bill at his 26th birthday (Volume 5, Page 90)
    - The unedited version of my editorial on LaRouche (Volume 5, Page 91)
    - An edited version of my editorial on LaRouche (Volume 5, Page 92)
    - Surprize! Koop is watching you! (Volume 5, Page 93)
    - Interview with me and a Review of Notes... in Edge, West Coast distribution (Volume 5, Page 94)
    - Lon & Bill at an amusement park, summer `88 (Volume 5, Page 95)
    - Bill & family during his first hospitalization (Volume 5, Page 96)
    - Bill at home after his first hospitalization (Volume 5, Page 97)
    - Bill & Lon together again after Bill's second hospitalization (Volume 5, Page 97)
    - Bill after his second hospitalization (Volume 5, Page 98)
    - Lon after Bill's second hospitalization (Fall, 1988) (Volume 5, Page 98)
    - Our 7th year anniversary (Volume 5, Page 99)
    - Flowers to Bill during his third hospitalization (Winter, 1988) (Volume 5, Page 100)